[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
In this module, we've seen how regression can be used to predict house prices and
在这个模块当中 我们已经了解了 回归分析是如何被运用来预测房屋价格的 并且
also be useful in a wide range of other applications.
回归分析在一个很广的领域内都有着应用
So, in the introduction to this course, Carlos introduced this machine
在这门课程的引言中 卡洛斯也提到了这个
learning pipeline, where we go from data, which gets shoved
机器学习的流水线 我们从数据开始出发 把数据塞进
into some machine learning method, and we use that to derive intelligence.
一些机器学习的方法里面 然后我们通过它来产生智能
Well, let's dig into this block diagram and expand it, now that we've seen
好的 让我们深入这幅框图 然后扩展它 现在我们已经见过了
these some of these machine learning tools, in a little bit more detail.
一些机器学习的工具 并且稍稍地探讨了一些细节
Okay, so now we know what we actually use to fit our data is some training data set,
所以现在我们已经知道了 事实上用来拟合 我们的模型的是那些训练集里的数据
so that's gonna be our data.
所以那些会作为我们的数据
And in our housing application,
在我们房屋的应用当中
where we're going to predict the price of some house,
我们要预测的是房屋的价格
the data that we collected was, we had this table of the house ID,
我们收集的数据是这样的 我们有一张包含房屋编号的表
and some set of house attributes, as well as the house's sales price.
其中还包含了一组房屋的属性 以及屋子的售价
And we had this for a whole bunch of houses in our neighborhood, and
我们对我们社区周围一大簇的房屋收集这样的数据 然后
we collected this data into some table.
我们把收集到的数据填入一张表中
So, that represented our training data set.
这张表就代表了我们的训练集
And then we took that data, and what we did was shoved it through some feature
然后我们拿着这些数据 我们所做的是把它们塞进一些特征
extractor, which in this case is a very simple feature extractor,
提取器 在这个例子当中是一个非常简单的特征提取器
where we just choose some subset of the house attributes.
我们仅仅是从房屋的属性当中选取一些作为特征
So, in the examples we looked at, X, our set of features,
在这个例子当中 我们会着眼于我们的特征集合 X
represented things, like, we looked at square feet of the house,
这些特征代表了一些事物 比如我们会考察房屋的平方英尺数
and we also looked at number of bathrooms.
我们同样还会考察卫生间的数量
And we talked about possibly using more features.
我们还会讨论使用更多特征的可能性
Again, we'll talk about that more in the regression course, but
同样的 我们会在回归分析的课程当中来更多地讨论 但是
those were two that we examined in this module.
在这个模块中我们只会考察那两个特征
And so then, what did we do with these features?
那么我们会用这些特征来做些什么呢？
Well, our goal was to take these features and
我们的目标是 运用这些特征 并且
have some type of model that led to a prediction of the house price.
得到一个能够预测房屋价格的某种类型的模型
Okay, so our output, the intelligence that
好的 所以我们的输出 也就是
we're deriving, is the predicted house price.
我们所产生出的智能 就是房屋价格的预测值
And we're going to do this for every house in our training data set.
我们会对我们训练集中的每一个房屋都作这样的特征提取
We're gonna take its associated features, and
并且我们会带着它们的特征一起
shove it through this machine learning model, and predict the house price.
把它们塞进这个机器学习的模型 并得到预测的房屋价格
And what's the machine learning model we talked about?
那么我们所讨论的机器学习模型是什么呢？
Well, in this case, it's regression.
在这个案例中 是回归分析
That's our specific machine learning model that we're looking at here.
这就是我们在这里所关注的具体的机器学习模型
Okay, but remember that this machine learning model had some set of parameters.
但是要记住 这个机器学习的模型有一组参数
Okay, so the parameters we call W.
我们把这组参数叫做W
These are the weights on our features.
它们是在我们的特征上所加的权重
So, for example, it's the weight on square feet or number of bathrooms, and so on.
举例来说 这个权重对应的是平房英尺数或者是卫生间个数 等等
More technically, these are called regression coefficients.
更严格来说 这些参数被叫做回归系数
And we talked about estimating these parameters from data,
我们所讨论的就是从数据中去估计这些参数
so our W hat is our estimate of these parameters.
所以我们的W就是我们对这些参数的估计
And how did we talk about doing that?
那么我们是怎么做估计的呢？
Well, we took our predicted output, so
我们取出我们的预测结果
our predicted house price, and we compared it to the true house price.
也就是预测的房屋价格 然后我们把它和真实价格相比较
So, the actual sales price that we recorded in our training data table.
也就是我们记录在我们的训练数据表中的 真实的售价
So, Y, here, is our actual sales
这里的Y就代表真实售价
price for the houses in our training data.
我们训练集中房屋的真实售价
And we compare to the predicted house price.
然后我们把它和预测的房屋价格相比较
And we use a quality metric to measure how well we're doing with our prediction,
我们使用了一种评价标准去衡量我们的预测是否够好
using our model, using W hat as the parameters of that model.
也就是用W hat作为参数的那个模型预测得是否够好
Well, how well are we doing?
那么我们做得怎么样呢？
What was the error metric we talked about?
我们所讨论过的损失的度量方式又是什么呢？
The error metric we talked about was something called residual sum of squares,
我们所讨论过的损失度量方式叫做残差平方和
where we just sum up the square difference between the actual house sales price and
我们把真实的房屋售价和预测售价的差的平方加起来
the predicted house sales price, summing over all houses in our training data set.
在我们的整个训练集的房屋上进行求和
Okay, so our quality metric is gonna take our predictions and
好的 所以我们的评价标准会使用我们的预测结果
our actual house sales observations, spit out this error, and
以及真实的房屋售价 计算并输出损失
it's gonna go into a machine learning algorithm that's gonna be used to update
这个损失会输入一个机器学习的算法 这个算法用来更新
the weights, update our parameters of our model.
那些权重 也就是更新我们模型的参数
And we're gonna talk about this machine learning algorithm, or
我们会讨论这个机器学习的算法
different variants of it, a lot more in the actual course on regression.
或者其他一些不同的变种更多一点 在我们的回归分析的课程中
But this is the overall flowchart for this machine learning method for
但这就是一个机器学习算法的完整的流程图
our house prediction problem.
对于我们的房价预测问题来说
And this loop here, where we're taking our predictions,
在这边的这条回路中 我们使用了我们的预测结果
computing our error relative to the actual house sales prices,
然后相对于真实的房屋售价去计算了损失
and updating the weights or our model parameters.
接着更新了我们的模型的权重
This process tends to happen in an iterative way,
这个过程常常是以一种迭代的方式进行
where we update values again and again.
我们会不断地更新权重
Okay, so if we abstract a way, what we see is we have some training data set.
好的 如果我们抽象地来看的话 我们会看到的是我们有训练数据集
We have some feature extraction process.
我们有一个特征提取的过程
We have some machine learning model.
我们有一些的机器学习模型
And it's gonna produce some intelligence, which in this case is a prediction.
并且它会表现出一些智能 在这个例子中就是预测结果
And we're gonna assess the quality of our intelligence with some quality measure.
接着我们会用一些评价标准去衡量 这个机器学习模型所产生出的智能的好坏
And we're gonna use that error or accuracy, depending which way we're
我们所使用的会是损失或者是正确率 这依赖于
thinking about measuring it, to adjust our model parameters using some algorithm.
我们考虑去度量它的方式 然后我们用一些算法来调整模型的参数
And we're gonna see this type of flow for machine learning again and again.
我们将会一再地看到这样的关于机器学习的流程
In this module, we've seen how to take our data and
在这个模块中 我们已经了解到了如何使用我们的数据
derive intelligence using something called regression,
通过一种叫做回归分析的方法去产生出智能
where we have a model that relates our features to our output.
我们有一个能够把输入的特征和输出相关联起来的模型
And we talked about this in the context of predicting house values, and
然后我们在预测房屋价格这个情景下讨论了这个模型
you also work through a really interesting IPython notebook.
同时你们也体验了十分有趣的 IPython notebook
And from this, you should be able to deploy really interesting regression
从现在起 你们应该有能力去部署一个十分有趣的回归分析
models in practice now.
模型到实际生活中了
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community